Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Press Secretary Files, 1978-2003; Series III
  - Photographs, 1978-1994; Subseries 4
    - Event Photos, Identified People, Constituents
      - U.S. Small Business Administration Luncheon, May 1981 (Box-folder 234/10)
      - Swearing-in Ceremony, Undated (Box-folder 234/11)
      - Al Swift's Congressional Listening Post Event at Sno-Isle VocationalSkills Center, Jan 1980 (Box-folder 234/12)
      - U.S. House of Representatives Event, Undated (Box-folder 234/13)
      - U.S.S. Henry M. Jackson Commission, 1985 (Box-folder 234/14)
      - Washington State Delegation, 102nd Congress, Undated (Box-folder 234/15)
      - Campaign Event, 1979 (Box-folder 234/16)
      - Campaign Event: Lopez and Orcas Islands, Jul 1985 (Box-folder 234/17)
      - Campaign Event, 1986 (Box-folder 234/18)
      - Campaign Event, 1986 (Box-folder 234/19)
      - Campaign Event, Undated (Box-folder 234/20)
      - Campaign Event, Undated (Box-folder 234/21)
      - Mike Caldwell, Lynnwood City Councilman, Undated (Box-folder 234/22)
      - Jimmy Carter, Jun 1979 (Box-folder 234/23)
      - Paula and Ms. Lilian Carter, Oct 1978 (Box-folder 234/24)
      - Group Shots: Constituents and Politicians, 1986 (Box-folder 234/25)
      - Constituent Photos, Oct 1979 (Box-folder 234/26)
      - Constituent Photos, Washington, D.C., circa 1980 (Box-folder 234/27)
      - Constituent Photos, Dec 1981 (Box-folder 234/28)
      - Constituent Photos, Washington, D.C., Undated (Box-folder 234/29)
      - Constituent Photos, Undated (Box-folder 234/30)
      - Constituent Photos, Undated (Box-folder 234/31)
      - Constituent Photos, Undated (Box-folder 234/32)
    - Al Swift Political Activities Photos
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/1)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/2)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/3)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/4)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/5)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/6)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/7)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/8)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/9)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/10)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/11)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/12)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 235/13)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/1)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/2)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/3)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/4)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/5)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/6)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/7)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/8)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/9)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/10)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/11)
      - Al Swift Political Activities, Undated (Box-folder 236/12)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/1)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/2)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/3)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/4)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/5)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/6)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/7)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/8)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/9)
      - Al Swift Political Activities (includes slides), Undated (Box-folder 237/10)
    - Congressional Photos
      Note: Includes contact sheets and negatives.
      - Photos from 98th Congress, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 238/1)
      - Photos from 99th Congress, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 238/2)
      - Photos from 100th Congress, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 239/1)
      - Photos from 101st Congress, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 239/2)
      - Photos from 101st Congress, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 240/1)
      - Photos from 102nd Congress, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 240/2)
      - Photos from 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 241/1)
      - Negatives, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 241/2)
    - Oversized Photos
      - Al Swift Political Activities, 1979-1994 (Box 242)
  - Audio Recordings, 1979-1994; Subseries 5
    - Cassettes
      - KPLU Election Spot, 1992 (Box-folder 243/1)
      - NPR Morning Edition: Report on Uniform Poll Closing Bill, Jan 1986 (Box-folder 243/2)
      - Press Briefing: A.T.and T. (H.R.5158), Undated (Box-folder 243/3)
      - NFR Report on Marine Shale/NAS Whidbey Tape, Undated (Box-folder 243/4)
      - Northwest Week in Review: Steve Forrester, Feb 1987 (Box-folder 243/5)
      - Actualities, 8/29/85-1/8/86 (Box-folder 243/6)
      - Uniform Poll Closing Mark Up at House Committee on Administration Meeting (H.R.3525)/Impromptu Press Conference After H.R.3525, 10/23/1985 (Box-folder 243/7)
      - Northwest Power Bill/Plans, 1985 (Box-folder 243/8)
      - Democratic Response (Reagan Speech): Al Swift, 2/12/1983 (Box-folder 243/9)
      - Radio Spots, 1979-81 (Box-folder 243/10)
      - Health Care Forums, Undated (Box-folder 243/11)
      - Voter Registration Hearing with Jesse Jackson, 3/21/1989 (Box-folder 243/12)
      - Voter Registration Hearing with Jesse Jackson, 3/21/1989 (Box-folder 243/13)
      - Speech to NAROB, 9/15/1988 (Box-folder 243/14)
      - Radio as Released, Dec 1982-Jul 1983 (Box-folder 243/15)
      - Port Angeles Chamber of Commerce Tapes by Al Swift, 1985-86 (Box-folder 243/16)
      - The Larry King Show: Term Limits (Al Swift), 8/7/1992 (Box-folder 243/17)
      - "For the Record" KING TV, 1983 (Box-folder 243/18)
      - Impact: KGMI with Rep. Al Swift, 7/5/1985 (Box-folder 243/19)
      - Swift Campaign Spots, 1988 (Box-folder 243/20)
      - KPAL Programming, 7/16/1987 (Box-folder 243/21)
      - Impact: KGMI with Jim Klauder 1984 Campaign, 6/28/1984 (Box-folder 243/22)
      - Public Service Announcements: Voice Wraps, 1989-91 (Box-folder 243/23)
      - "Joe Slade White's Greatest Hits--1989", 1989 (Box-folder 243/24)
      - Nordlinger Associates, Washington D.C.: Twelve Political Radio Spots, Undated (Box-folder 243/25)
      - United We Stand, Undated (Box-folder 243/26)
      - Steve Forrester's Northwest Week in Review: With Al Swift--Misc. Topics, 1986 (Box-folder 243/27)
      - Raw Swift: #9 and #10, Undated (Box-folder 243/28)
      - Raw Swift: #11 and #12, 1983 (Box-folder 243/29)
      - Northwest Political Science Speech--"Congress: Institution in Transition or Crisis?" by Al Swift, 10/29/1982 (Box-folder 243/30)
      - Discussion Before Congressional Interns on Congressional Leadership, Reform and Followership: Week Following FBI/ABSCAM News, 1980 (Box-folder 243/31)
      - Swift/Snider (10/31/80) KBRC and Swift/Weaver (11/10/80) KOMO-- Northwest Power Bill, 1980 (Box-folder 243/32)
      - Raw Swift: #1 and #2, Undated (Box-folder 243/33)
      - Raw Swift, 6/10/1980 (Box-folder 243/34)
      - Raw Swift: #3 and #4, Undated (Box-folder 243/35)
      - Raw Swift, Nov 1983 (Box-folder 243/36)
      - Tim Douglas, Undated (Box-folder 243/37)
      - 101st Congress: Packages, Undated (Box-folder 243/38)
      - Raw Swift: Malcom Baldridge Telephones, Undated (Box-folder 243/39)
      - Announcement Speech, 1984 (Box-folder 243/40)
      - Reagan Radio Address and Response by Al Swift, 2/12/1983 (Box-folder 243/41)
      - Voice Wraps, Undated (Box-folder 243/42)
      - Voice Demos, Undated (Box-folder 243/43)
      - Radio as Released, Apr 1981-Oct 1982 (Box-folder 243/44)
      - Adress to JJ Dinner, 11/5/1983 (Box-folder 243/45)
      - Swift Package on Packaging from Olympia (Testimony), 1992 (Box-folder 243/46)
      - Speech to Washington State Labor Council, 1992 (Box-folder 243/47)
      - Swift on Health, GATT, and the Environment, Undated (Box-folder 243/48)
      - Radio as Released, Jul 1983-Feb 1984 (Box-folder 243/49)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor #1, Undated (Box-folder 243/50)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor #2, Undated (Box-folder 243/51)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor #3, Undated (Box-folder 243/52)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor #4, Undated (Box-folder 243/53)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor #5, Undated (Box-folder 243/54)
      - Swift Speech to FCBA, Sep 1987 (Box-folder 243/55)
      - Mix Tape, Undated (Box-folder 243/56)
      - Base Closing Commission/Campaign Finance Reform Hearing, 5/21/1991 (Box-folder 243/57)
      - Press Conference by Jack Mitchell on Richard Starr, 2/13/1980 (Box-folder 243/58)
      - Northwest Power Bill: Mark Up--Full Committee, 3/19/1980 (Box-folder 243/59)
      - Lowry, Mike, Undated (Box-folder 243/60)
      - Radio as Released, Jun-Sep 1984 (Box-folder 243/61)
      - Floor Debate on Motor Voter Conference: EPA Testimony-THM Subcommittee, May 1993 (Box-folder 244/1)
      - Actualities: (9-10), 1985 (Box-folder 244/2)
      - Weekly Port Angeles Chamber of Commerce with Al Swift, 1985 (Box-folder 244/3)
      - Child Abuse Radio Spots, Undated (Box-folder 244/4)
      - Base Closure Commission: Swift Testimony, Presidential Debates #1: Election Subcommittee, Undated (Box-folder 244/5)
      - Uniform Poll Closing: U.S. News and World Report/Northwest Week in Review, 1986 (Box-folder 244/6)
      - Swift Testimony on U.S. Embassy in China: 6/15/89, Swift and Obey Response to President Bush's Campaign Finance Reform Proposal--Press Gallery, 1989 (Box-folder 244/7)
      - Clean Air Press Conference, 1990 (Box-folder 244/8)
      - BPA and Federal Facilities, Undated (Box-folder 244/9)
      - "The Most Beautiful Lady in the World", 1986 (Box-folder 244/10)
      - Motor Voter Floor Debate/Hearing, Feb 1993 (Box-folder 244/11)
      - KISD Radio Interview Testimony: U.S. International Trade Commission--Relief for U.S. Shake and Shingle Industry, KING Live Radio Interview, Undated (Box-folder 244/12)
      - Radio Release, Jan 1985 (Box-folder 244/13)
      - Full First Amendment Rights for Broadcasters: "American Women in Radio and Television"--Speech by Al Swift, Undated (Box-folder 244/14)
      - FENN and KING: Swift for Congress--"Endorse", Undated (Box-folder 244/15)
      - NPR All Things Considered: "Al Swift Carries On", 1994 (Box-folder 244/16)
      - Port Angeles Chamber of Commerce: Uniform Poll Closing, Taxes, Undated (Box-folder 244/17)
      - Impact Radio Program, Undated (Box-folder 244/18)
      - High Definition Television: What Will Congress Do?, 1989 (Box-folder 244/19)
      - Mixing Tape #2, Undated (Box-folder 244/20)
      - Uniform Poll Closing Package, Undated (Box-folder 244/21)
      - "Swift Tape", Undated (Box-folder 244/22)
      - Presidential Debates #2: Response to Everett Naval Station Being Taken Off the Base Closure List, Jun 1993 (Box-folder 244/23)
      - Northwest Week in Review: Superfund Legislation and Poll Closing Bills, 1985 (Box-folder 244/24)
      - Political Spots, 1982 (Box-folder 244/25)
      - Speech: League of Women Voters, 8/13/1981 (Box-folder 244/26)
      - Congressman Al Swift: Re-election statement (2:52), 1992 (Box-folder 244/27)
      - Radio Appearances, 1984-85 (Box-folder 244/28)
      - Everett Hearing: FCC Access Charge Decision--Public Forum Parts 1 and 2, 1983 (Box-folder 244/29)
      - Everett Hearing: FCC Access Charge Decision--Public Forum Parts 3 and 4, 1983 (Box-folder 244/30)
      - Everett Hearing: FCC Access Charge Decision--Public Forum Parts 5 and 6, 1983 (Box-folder 244/31)
      - Northwest Power Bill: House Floor Tape #6 (Final), Undated (Box-folder 244/32)
      - Swift Spots, Undated (Box-folder 244/33)
      - Radio Spots: "TV Kids," "Balance," and "Power.", 1988 (Box-folder 244/34)
      - The Clean Air Working Group: 60 Second Radio Commercial, Undated (Box-folder 244/35)
      - Election Subcommittee: Accessibility to Polls--Oversight Hearing, 1987 (Box-folder 244/36)
      - Rail Safety Press Conference with FRA Administrator Jolene Molitories, 1994 (Box-folder 244/37)
      - PAC of C.: D.C. Government, 1986 (Box-folder 244/38)
      - Dub: Excerpts from Northwest Week in Review, 1985 (Box-folder 244/39)
      - Northwest Week in Review, 1986 (Box-folder 244/40)
      - Issues: Hanford Nuclear Waste Site, Undated (Box-folder 244/41)
      - Al Swift for Congress: 4 Thirty Second Spots, Undated (Box-folder 244/42)
      - Al Swift: Northwest Power Act Press Conference with Morrison, Undated (Box-folder 244/43)
      - NASA, Undated (Box-folder 244/44)
      - Raw Swift, Undated (Box-folder 244/45)
      - China Trip: Women's Political Caucus and the League of Women Voters, Undated (Box-folder 244/46)
      - Northwest Week in Review, 1/31/1985 (Box-folder 244/47)
      - Northwest Week in Review, 4/18/1985 (Box-folder 244/48)
      - Northwest Week in Review, 4/25/1985 (Box-folder 244/49)
      - PACs/Shakes and Shingles/Tax Reform, 1986 (Box-folder 244/50)
      - KBAE: "30 Minutes in Snohomish County" Al Swift Guest Floor Statement: China-U.S. Nuclear Agreement, Floor Debate: Uniform Poll Closing, Dec 1985 (Box-folder 244/51)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 244/52)
      - Port Angeles Chamber of Commerce, Dec 1985 (Box-folder 244/53)
      - Ezra Benson: "The Proper Role of Government", Undated (Box-folder 244/54)
      - Strawberry Hearing, 5/20/1980 (Box-folder 244/55)
      - U.S. Forest Service: RARE II and Boulder River, 1981 (Box-folder 244/56)
      - KPUG Newsmakers: Paula Swift on the U.S.S.R., 11/22/1987 (Box-folder 244/57)
      - Northwest Week in Review, 3/7/1985 (Box-folder 244/58)
      - Uniform Poll Closing Interviews: Everett Navy Homeport, 1986 (Box-folder 244/59)
      - Swift: Late, 1979 (Box-folder 244/60)
      - Impact: Jim Klauder, Undated (Box-folder 244/61)
      - Demo Reply, Undated (Box-folder 244/62)
      - Raw Swift: #5 and #6, Undated (Box-folder 244/63)
      - Reagan/Houchen Ads, 10/14/1982 (Box-folder 244/64)
      - Swift, Undated (Box-folder 244/65)
    - Reel to Reel
      - Al Swift Primary: (3 30 Second Spots) #18, 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 245/1)
      - "Endorse Al Swift for Congress": (60 Second Spot) Master, Undated (Box-folder 245/2)
      - Al Swift: Primary (3 30 Second Spots), 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 245/3)
      - Al Swift: General Election (4 30 Second Spots), 11/28/1986 (Box-folder 245/4)
      - Al Swift: "Universal", 10/19/1992 (Box-folder 245/5)
      - Al Swift: General Election (4 30 Second Spots) Hold til Ordered, 7/13/1983 (Box-folder 245/6)
      - Al Swift: General Election (2 30 Second Spots) Immediate til End of Campaign Even Rotation, Undated (Box-folder 245/7)
      - Al Swift: General Election, 11/28/1986 (Box-folder 245/8)
      - Al Swift: (3 30 Second Spots), 10/30/86-11/3/86 (Box-folder 245/9)
      - KISM Al Swift: Primary (3 30 Second Spots), 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 245/10)
      - #10 Master: Al Swift, Undated (Box-folder 245/11)
      - Al Swift for Congress: 4 Takes--Disclaimer, Undated (Box-folder 245/12)
      - Paula Swift 30 Second Public Service Announcement--Constitution Bicentennial, 1987 (Box-folder 245/13)
      - Al Swift: Primary (4 30 Secon Spots), 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 245/14)
      - KAYO/KJMD Al Swift for Congress: (4 30 Second Spots)*, Up Close Swift, Undated (Box-folder 245/15)
        *Two tapes are located in this box.
      - Democratic Response: Al Swift, 2/12/1983 (Box-folder 245/16)
    - Cassettes
      - News Segment with Swift re: impact of projecting election results; Washington Women in Timber, Undated (Box-folder 246/1)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/2)
      - Swift commentary on Farmer's Home Administration issues, Undated (Box-folder 246/3)
      - Swift commentary on base closure; radio frequency allotments, Undated (Box-folder 246/4)
      - Capitol Newsbeat interview with Swift re: Motorvoter legislation, projecting election results, etc., Undated (Box-folder 246/5)
      - Swift speech before House of Representatives re: projecting election results, Undated (Box-folder 246/6)
      - Swift commentary re: Railroad labor issues, etc., Undated (Box-folder 246/7)
      - Music, unidentified, Undated (Box-folder 246/8)
      - Swift, Undated (Box-folder 246/9)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/10)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/11)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/12)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/13)
      - KAYO: Regional Power Bill, 2/27/1980 (Box-folder 246/14)
      - Questions and Answers: Swift, Undated (Box-folder 246/15)
      - "Roughs": Opens and Closes, 10/14/1986 (Box-folder 246/16)
      - Swift commentary re: FCC legislation, Undated (Box-folder 246/17)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box-folder 246/18)
      - FCC legislation, Undated (Box-folder 246/19)
      - Rosenberg, Undated (Box-folder 246/20)
      - Al Swift on President Clinton's State of the Union Address, Undated (Box-folder 246/21)
      - Swift for Congress: The Real Issues, Undated (Box-folder 246/22)
      - Al Swift: 30 Second Spots, Undated (Box-folder 246/23)
      - KRKO AM 1380: Al Swift Primary (4 30 Second Spots), Undated (Box-folder 246/24)
      - Swift interview re: FCC legislation, Undated (Box-folder 246/25)
      - Al Swift: General Election (4 30 Second Spots), Jan-86 (Box-folder 246/26)
      - Swift: General Spot, Undated (Box-folder 246/27)
      - Five Leading Journalists Critique the State of the Union Address and the State of the Union, Undated (Box-folder 246/28)
      - Compliation created by Al Swift including a speech given at Federal Building during Kent State Week (circa 2000), Reaction to John Kennedy's Death (1952), Snapshot of Bellingham's "civic inferiority complex" in the late 1950s., circa 1950; circa 2000 (Box-folder 246/29)
    - Reel to Reel
      - RKO Radio 14: Al Swift (2 60 and 2 30 Second Spots), Undated (Box-folder 246/29)
      - Al Swift: Audio Portion, Undated (Box-folder 246/30)
      - KRKO: Al Swift for Congress/A Dramatization on the Issues, 1982 (Box-folder 246/31)
      - Swift for Congress: #5 and #6 (2 30 Second Spots) Master, 10/31/1984 (Box-folder 246/32)
      - Swift: Primary (4 30 Second Spots), 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 246/33)
      - Swift: Primary (3 30 Second Spots), 9/2/1986 (Box-folder 246/34)
      - KWYZ Voice Demos (Paul McCarthy), 8/6/1984 (Box-folder 246/35)
      - Senator Jackson Endorsement of Al Swift, Undated (Box-folder 246/36)
      - Al Swift Tag and Disclaimer (:07) 3 Cuts Radio 123 (8 Track Tape), Undated (Box-folder 246/37)
  - Video Recordings, 1979-2003; Subseries 6
    - VHS
      - Public Power Preference Clause (19:35), 9/7/1984 (Box-folder 247/1)
      - Public Power Preference Clause (20:00), Mar 1985 (Box-folder 247/2)
      - Edited Airchecks--Electromechanical--Upgrade of Announcement for Washington (9:40), 5/16/1985 (Box-folder 247/3)
      - John Fluke Speech: With Questions and Answers (60:00), 10/24/1986 (Box-folder 247/4)
      - Uniform Poll Closing Bill: House Debate and Vote Part 1, 1/29/1986 (Box-folder 247/5)
      - Uniform Poll Closing Bill: House Debate and Vote Part 2, 1/29/1986 (Box-folder 247/6)
      - Newsclips Part 1, Aug 1987 (Box-folder 247/7)
      - Newsclips Part 2, Aug 1987 (Box-folder 247/8)
      - Fairness Doctrine, 9/22/1987 (Box-folder 247/9)
      - Paula Swift Bicentennial Public Service Announcement (:30), Jun 1987 (Box-folder 247/10)
      - General Instrument News Release, Jun 1988 (Box-folder 247/11)
      - Swift Profile, Nov 1988 (Box-folder 248/1)
      - Pilchuck Yacht Club Regatta, 1988 (Box-folder 248/2)
      - The Olympic National Park (14:04), 1988 (Box-folder 248/3)
      - US West ISDN Program (10:08), 1/7/1988 (Box-folder 248/4)
      - Olympic National Park Fiftieth Anniversary Speech by Al Swift, 7/23/1988 (Box-folder 248/5)
      - Hanford: A National Asset (14:00), May 1988 (Box-folder 248/6)
      - Representative Schaefer's Washington Update: "Clean Air" (28:37), Sep 1989 (Box-folder 248/7)
      - Representatives Al Swift and Phil Sharp on Energy Policy (24:08), 6/15/1989 (Box-folder 248/8)
      - C-SPAN: Campaign Finance Reform, Jun 1989 (Box-folder 248/9)
      - You and PBS (37:00), 1/10/1989 (Box-folder 248/10)
      - National Association of Broadcasters--Satellite Show With Swift, Wyden, Packwood, and Gorton, circa 1989 (Box-folder 248/11)
      - Everett Navy Homeport, 11/9/1987 (Box-folder 249/1)
      - Northwest Timber/Fishing/Logging, 1/10/1989 (Box-folder 249/2)
      - US West Today H.R.2140 Betawest (30:00), Sep 1989 (Box-folder 249/3)
      - US West Today H.R.2140 Beatwest (30:00), Sep 1989 (Box-folder 249/4)
      - McNeil/Lehrer Newshour: Paula Swift and Congressional Wives, Warren Magnesun (KIRO), May 1989 (Box-folder 249/5)
      - Modified Final Judgement Legislative Forum (14:16), 2/13/1990 (Box-folder 249/6)
      - KOMO Town Meeting: Timber and the Spotted Owl (60:00), Apr 1990 (Box-folder 249/7)
      - Special Order on TV MARTI, Mar 1990 (Box-folder 249/8)
      - Blaine Border Hearings, 4/6/1990 (Box-folder 249/9)
      - C-SPAN: "Interview with Al Swift", 12/19/1990 (Box-folder 249/10)
      - U.S. House of Representatives Floor Coverage, 9/10/1990 (Box-folder 250/1)
      - Al Swift on VR Rule, 1/31/1990 (Box-folder 250/2)
      - C-SPAN--Term Limits, 11/7/1991 (Box-folder 250/3)
      - In Focus With Hank Brown (28:30), Nov 1991 (Box-folder 250/4)
      - Driftnets (22:15), 3/25/1991 (Box-folder 250/5)
      - Northwest Focus (KCPQ): Skagit River (30:00), 12/1/1991 (Box-folder 250/6)
      - Al Swift Tape--Various Stories (120:00), 6/91-7/23/91 (Box-folder 250/7)
      - King 5 News (5pm): Skagit: Wild and Scenic River (2 Cuts), 6/4/1991 (Box-folder 250/8)
      - TV MARTI Debate, Aug 1992 (Box-folder 250/9)
      - McNeil/Lehrer Newshour: Al Swift on Veto of Motor Voter, 6/6/1992 (Box-folder 250/10)
      - Motor Voter Debate, 6/25/1992 (Box-folder 250/11)
      - Saved NAS Widbey!, June/July 1991 (Box-folder 250/12)
      - Sumas Flood, 11/10/1990 (Box-folder 250/13)
      - Weyerhaueser Everett Pulp Mill: "Salute to Everett" (8:30), Mar 1992 (Box-folder 251/1)
      - House Post Office Task Force Floor Debate, 7/23/1992 (Box-folder 251/2)
      - "Presidential Campaigns: Can We Keep Them Clean and Relevant?" National Press Club, 1/16/1992 (Box-folder 251/3)
      - House Debate and Passage of Telemarketing Bill 1993, CENTEL Cosponsored Discussion on Congress, 1992, 1993 (Box-folder 251/4)
      - Reauthorization of RCRA--Washington Update, Mar 1992 (Box-folder 251/5)
      - Representative Swift and Senator Brock in JOC Hearing (9:00), 4/20/1993 (Box-folder 251/6)
      - Motor Voter Signing Ceremony at the White House, 5/20/1993 (Box-folder 251/7)
      - Motor Voter Debate 103rd Congress, 2/4/1993 (Box-folder 251/8)
      - RR #49 Committee Funding (14:28), 3/30/1993 (Box-folder 251/9)
      - Motor Voter Speech and Vote (16:36), 2/4/1993 (Box-folder 251/10)
      - C-SPAN: Viewer Call-in (Motor Voter), 2/2/1993 (Box-folder 251/11)
      - The Navy of the Future--Naval Station Everett (8:29), 5/28/1993 (Box-folder 252/1)
      - Swift on Campaign Finance Reform and the Superfund, 11/22/1993 (Box-folder 252/2)